http://www.scriptpro.com/privacy-policy

skip to contentlogo-text-scriptlogo-text-proCustomer SupportmoreSoftwareRoboticsSafetySupportFinancial PerformanceAbout UsContact UsDrug DatabaseBlogCareersScriptPro LibraryRFP RequestPrivacy PolicyPrivacy & Cookie PolicyYour privacy is important to ScriptPro, so we have developed a policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your information to anyone other than ScriptPro certified business units and business partners without your consent or as permitted by this Privacy Policy.Privacy PolicyHow can you stop receiving email from us?Each email contains an Unsubscribe link at the end, allowing you to remove yourself from the email list at any time.What Personal Information does ScriptPro collect?ScriptPro may collect information about you if you download certain documents from this site or register for information sponsored or co-sponsored by ScriptPro. This information could include your name, title, company name, e-mail address, phone number, work address, information about your job function, and information about your company. ScriptPro does not collect passwords and security information used for authentication and account access.How does ScriptPro use my personal information?The information ScriptPro collects through this website is used solely for the purpose of alerting you to ScriptPro news and information regarding products, solutions, services, and events offered by ScriptPro or offered jointly by ScriptPro and its business partners. This information may be shared with our business partners so that we may offer you the opportunity to review our joint solution offerings.How do I manage my personal information preferences?If you have any questions or concerns about ScriptPro's Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us. If you have subscribed to our marketing emails or other communications and wish to be removed from our mailing lists, you may unsubscribe at any time. UnsubscribeScriptPro uses Google AdWordsThis website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven't completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an inquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone's past visits to ScriptPro. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google's privacy policy.You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and you may opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.ScriptPro may update its Privacy Policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.Cookie PolicyWhat are Cookies?Also known as browser cookies or tracking cookies, cookies are small text files of letters and numbers that we put on your computer if you agree. These cookies allow us to distinguish you from other users of our website, which helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.Cookies are created when a user's browser loads a particular website. The website sends information to the browser which then creates a text file. Every time the user goes back to the same website, the browser retrieves and sends this file to the website's server. Computer cookies are created not just by the website the user is browsing but also by other websites that run advertisements, widgets, or other elements on the page being loaded. These cookies regulate how the advertisements appear or how the widgets and other elements function on the page.What Cookies are used on this Website?The table below explains the cookies we use and why:Cookie nameSourcePurposePardot <visitor_id accountid>Visitor CookieThe cookies include information about unique visitors and this data identifies this information for tracking particular visits. Pardot cookies store no personally identifying information; only a unique identifier._ga _gidGoogle AnalyticsThese cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.f.fbqFacebook PixelThese cookies are used for remarketing through facebook properties (Facebook and Instagram). The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited._linkedin_­partner_idLinkedIn Insight TagThese cookies are used for remarketing through LinkedIn. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.Who drops Cookies when you use our Website?Many of the cookies on our site are considered part of our services and are considered "first party cookies" (meaning cookies placed and read by us directly).Some of our partners also utilize cookies when you use our services. These specialist "third party cookies" are not set by us but are rather set by companies such as Google for website analytics purposes with our permission. Please read our partners' privacy policies to ensure that you are comfortable with the manner in which they use cookies.How do you Opt Out?If you do not consent to our use of cookies, you can set your browser settings to reject cookies. These settings are usually found in the "options" or "preferences" menu of your web browser. You can find more details about how to control cookies here. Alternatively, you can use the "Help" option in your web browser to get more details.A number of features of our services may not work or will be curtailed from working effectively without cookies. As a result, changing your browser settings to reject cookies may have a negative impact on your ability to use our website.If you use our website with your web browser set to accept cookies, you consent to our use of cookies as described in this cookies policy. If you do not accept our use of cookies, you should either (a) immediately stop using our services or (b) use the settings described above to reject cookies. You can find out more about deleting and blocking cookies here and using your web browser's "Help" option. (c) Click the following link Opt Out and submit information to our company and we will remove your information.Contacting UsIf you have any questions about this Policy, our practices relating to the website or your dealing with the website you can contact us.This website is optimized for modern browsers. For the best experience and fastest load times please use a newer browser to view this site.We recommend upgrading to one of the modern browsers below.ChromeEdgeFirefoxI understand, take me to the site anyway.
